Former Congressman Ramon dela Peña
remains at large.
Pieces of evidence show
that he is behind the murder
of his personnel, Lando Nakpil.
And to you, Ramon dela Peña,
your days are numbered.
- We've found it.
- Have you found Liam?
The safe house.
If something happens to your son,
he deserves it.
I don't care!
Your son should get what he deserves.
Hans, do it now!
Dad, go on! Help them escape.
Call the police.
Dad!
- Mom, look out for Joyce!
- Joyce!
- Go ahead! Try it, Ramon.
Are you following me?
Joyce?
What are you doing here?
I'm on vacation.
What about you? What are you doing here?
I'm on vacation too.
I forget that it is also
your dream to be in Paris.
Whatever your reason is for coming here,
I know it's not because of me.
Do you want to take a walk?
I took leave from the university
where I teach Creative Writing.
I'm taking my chance
to finish writing a book here.
A book?
Yeah...
Passion project. A novel.
I'm glad you've fulfilled your dreams.
Same with you, Joyce.
Your advocacy projects make me feel proud.
By the way, Joyce, I sent the...
The annulment papers to your house.
I didn't know you are here in Paris.
My mom told me about the papers.
I will sign when I get home.
Is it okay?
Is it okay to what?
Is it okay...
that I filed our annulment papers?
Yes.
We've been separated for three years.
It's just a formality.
There's no problem with it.
- But since we're already here...
- But...
Okay, go ahead.
You go first.
- You go first.
- Go ahead.
Sorry.
Hello, love?
Yes...
Yes.
Okay. I'll just fix...
I'll sign the papers when I get back
to the Philippines.
No... I'm busy.
Can I call you later?
My son...
You didn't warn me
that I'd see your dad here.
How can we move on, my son?
But, son, you know...
I'm happy for him.
I'm happy to see that
he has fulfilled all his dreams.
Maybe I was the one dragging him down.
But why am I being like this?
I have also fulfilled all my dreams, right?
Now, we're here.
I'm here in Paris, my son.
Now, I'm here in...
I'm here in the city of love.
While your dad is calling someone...
He's calling someone "love".
But, son...
Your mom isn't affected by it.
I'm really not.
Your dad is free to do anything.
Anything that can make him happy.
I have no right to stop him.
I no longer have the right.
I hope you understand.
I miss you.
I love you, son.
Bonjour! Je m'appelle Mark.
So, I will be your tour guide today.
Put your name tags and armbands on,
so we won't lose each other.
We're here in
one of the busiest places in Paris.
So, Mr. Gerald and I
are both wearing white bands.
Mr. Jaypee and Miss Joan
are wearing blue...
Oh, why does Miss Joyce
not have a partner?
Don't worry. There's another one coming.
Maybe we should just wait for him.
- Maybe...
- Sir, sir.
- I'm sorry, I'm late.
- You're right on time.
Please wear this, Mr. Liam.
So you will be Miss Joyce's buddy
for this tour.
So you're part of this tour, too?
Do you know each other?
Very well.
Okay, follow me.
Let's start the tour.
Come on.
You can't escape me this time,
like what you did yesterday.
I didn't escape from you.
You were busy with your phone, remember?
Yeah. I need to take care of
something at work back home.
Work? But you call her love.
What did you say, Joyce?
Nothing.
Mr. Liam, Miss Joyce, let's go.
Oui. S'il vous plait.
This is one of my personal favorites
here in Paris.
The Pont Alexandre III,
or Alexander III Bridge.
This was a gift from Russia to France
as a symbol of their strong friendship
and alliance.
It only proves that in love,
everything is possible.
So no one should give up
when there are challenges.
Well said, Miss Joyce.
But you should know
when to give up a fight.
I agree, especially if it's a losing game.
You should concede.
Sir Liam, what kind of fights
should we give up?
The fight where you feel you're alone.
Maybe we should take a lunch break.
I'll give you an hour.
You're free to roam around.
There are restaurants near here.
And let's see each other in the van.
But please, be on time.
And you should stick together.
Okay?
Hey.
We should stick together.
Can we just meet by the van?
I'll roam around alone.
I also researched about Paris.
Do you want me to give you a tour?
It's my dream to be here, Liam.
I know everything that you will say.
Wow. Okay.
We'll see.
Did you know that there
are 32 candelabras here?
So imagine how bright this place is
during night-time.
And there are also sea creatures and cherubs.
But if I were Engineers Résal and Alby,
I would make a monument for
the most beautiful woman I've ever met.
Are you trying to piss me off?
You're so serious. I'm just happy.
You deserve a monument
for all the good things you've done
through your foundation.
So you really are teasing me.
Life's greatest happiness
is to be convinced we are loved.
What?
It's not good if you're just
convincing yourself, right?
Especially if you're the only one fighting.
Liam, wait.
What is with the insinuations?
Is that about our past?
Wait.
Why are you blaming me?
It's one of the famous quotes of
the romantic writer, Victor Hugo.
Is your name Victor?
I'm just kidding.
But you know what, Joyce?
I want to tell you so many things
you don't know yet.
Hello, love?
Yes.
- Yes...
- Love, my foot.
Yes, Joyce?
What's the problem this time?
My gosh, Odet.
How can I have fun here?
Of all people, it's Liam who I encountered
here in Paris.
He did nothing but piss me off the whole day.
What did he do to you?
All he did was say things
about our failed marriage.
I thought it was a mutual decision
when you separated?
I'll back out from this tour
if I lose my patience.
Can I just return to Manila?
Go alone if you're really pissed off.
Admit it. You want to be with Liam, too!
You meet Liam out of all the million people
in Paris.
Fate really has its own way!
Please tell "fate" not to interfere
with my moving on!
Joyce, may I remind you,
I'm not your marriage and family therapist.
I'm your foundation's secretary.
Okay, Joyce?
Aside from putting on my makeup,
I have prepared everything for the mountains
you will climb to give out school supplies.
What happened to you?
Odet, wait...
Where am I?
Odet, I'm lost! I don't know where I am.
What? My gosh, Joyce!
Wait, where's Miss Joyce?
I also don't know.
Every time I talk to someone on the phone,
she goes missing.
I told you there's a buddy system.
You should stick with each other.
What do we do now?
I'm sorry, Sir. Don't worry...
I'll look for her.
I won't go with you
to your last destination.
Okay, let us know
if you find Miss Joyce, okay?
- Okay. Be safe.
- Be safe, too.
Let's go.
Where did you go, Joyce?
Joyce!
Joyce, come on!
Where have you been?
We've been looking for you.
I went to get some fresh air.
Get some fresh air?
We shouldn't leave each other, Joyce.
Why do you keep leaving me alone?
Let's go.
You're funny.
What's your problem?
Is this what you want, Liam?
Fine, let's speak in innuendos.
Tell me.
Was I really the one who left?
Joyce...
Why? That's the truth.
Liam, who wanted to break us up?
Joyce, my only point is,
you went missing while I was on the phone.
That's all.
Stop gaslighting me, Liam.
Stop it. Tell me everything you want to say!
Get straight to the point!
This confrontation is already
three years overdue, anyway.
To be fair,
you even chose such a beautiful location!
Okay, Joyce.
What do you want to talk about?
Tell me.
I want to talk about us, Liam.
I want to understand why you're mad at me.
Tell me everything.
Okay, Joyce.
I'll admit that when I saw you here...
I felt embarrassed.
Seeing you reminded me of all my mistakes!
All my shortcomings!
That it was my fault that our son died!
Liam, you're not the only one
who suffered when Dex died.
I thought we would grieve together.
I thought we would go through it together.
But what did you do?
What did you do? You left me!
Liam, I knew that I shouldn't give up on you.
It was hard, Liam.
You don't know how hard it was, Liam.
Liam, it was so painful when I lost my child.
It's also painful that I lost a husband.
For the last time, before we separate...
let's try not to fight.
Here.
Thank you.
Can we start the tour again?
You're right.
If this is where we end things...
we should at least end it happily.
Your ice cream might turn salty
because of your tears.
Try it.
Yes, it's salty.
Salty?
I told you.
Your tears.
You should have this.
Why?
So you can taste my sadness.
Joyce, we don't have to be sad.
Honestly, I'm happy.
Because, finally, after three years,
we let out our resentments
towards each other.
So, are we okay now?
How can we be okay?
We're no longer part of the tour.
Where do we go now?
We can make our own itinerary.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Joyce, hurry up.
Liam, wait. We've been walking forever.
Where are we going?
You will like this.
Wait.
Excuse me. I'm wearing heels.
My feet hurt already.
Come on. Hurry up!
Let's go!
You can do it.
Liam.
Why did you wear heels?
Because this is Paris!
Come on!
Let's go. Hurry!
You will be surprised
with what I will show you.
What is it?
Just wait.
Here.
Welcome to the bridge of romance.
It's so beautiful.
Eiffel Tower isn't the only beautiful thing
here in Paris.
Joyce...
I realized that a story isn't whole
if it's only one-sided.
There are many reasons why
I should ask your forgiveness.
I also realized that I was
so focused on my own suffering.
Maybe that's why I gave up on us.
I forgot about our happy memories together.
I forgot how happy I was
when I was with you.
I forgot to look at the bigger picture.
I shouldn't have let anger
get the better of me.
I wish I didn't leave you.
I wish we faced together Dex's passing.
Liam, there's something I want to tell you.
Joyce...
If it will only make me sad...
can you not say it anymore?
Can you let me be happy this time?
So I'll have happy memories before I...
before I set you free.
If only I could stop the hands of time.
Hurry up!
If only I could, Liam.
I would do it.
Liam, can I ask you a question?
What is it?
No, never mind.
Come on, Joyce...
Tell me, what is it?
Never mind.
What is it? Tell me.
The one you call "love".
Love...
Well, wait. Where do I start?
- Liam.
- Yes?
Champ de Mars is so big.
You can start from the beginning.
Okay, fine.
Love is a good person.
She's always happy.
Is she pretty?
Yes, she is.
Hardworking.
Diligent.
Most of all, you can always ask her a favor.
What?
Love is my co-teacher
at the university where I teach.
She's Professor Lovely de Leon,
also known as Love.
She's taking all my teaching loads
while I'm on leave.
Love is your co-worker?
Yes.
But are you together?
What do you mean?
Come on. Love is already married.
Wait...
Was that why you walked out on me?
Oh, Joyce!
Are you jealous?
Excuse me?
Wow!
I'm not...
I'm not jealous.
I no longer have the right to get jealous.
Do you want me to give it to you?
Give me what?
The right to get jealous.
I couldn't ask for more, Liam.
So don't make my hopes up.
What matters is we were given
a chance to start over again.
Start over again?
Yes.
Think about it.
This is where I found the old Liam...
in Paris, France.
The Liam...
I admired.
The Liam who has confidence in himself.
The Liam I entrusted my life with.
Don't you have any regrets?
After all that we've been through?
Nothing.
Dex wouldn't want us to live
a life full of regrets and anger.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, we should be happy.
Come on. You don't have to apologize.
Honestly, I'm happy.
I'm happy to hear everything you said.
Maybe that's what
I've been wanting to hear...
That I can live without regrets.
Liam, it's hard to live...
with a desire to change something
in your past.
We only have the future.
Joyce, sorry.
What for?
Sorry that I left you.
Sorry, too, because...
Because?
I can't help it.
You can't help what?
I still love you.
Until now...
you're still the one.
If only I could rewrite my story...
I wish I was a star.
So I could have spent
millions of years with them.
Liam, are you okay?
What's going on with you?
- Joyce...
- Liam?
Joyce.
Joyce, I dreamed of everything.
The typewriter changed our life, Joyce.
I saw everything.
I remembered everything.
Joyce, I need to find the typewriter.
I need to bring Dex back to life!
- I need to bring Dex back to life, Joyce!
- I threw the typewriter away.
- It's gone.
- Joyce, why did you throw it away?
I need to bring Dex back to life!
Liam.
That is not the solution, Liam.
Joyce... Joyce, why...
Why did you bring us back here?
Why did you bring us back to the point
where I'm writing?
Why didn't you...
Why didn't you bring Dex back to life?
You know there is a price to pay!
We don't need the typewriter, Liam.
The solution lies in how we will stay strong
despite all the tragedies in our life!
The two of us, not the typewriter!
I'm sorry, Joyce.
I understand.
I understand everything you said.
Now...
all we can do is be strong for Dex.
Let's make our son's life meaningful.
Joyce...
I love you so much.
So much.
I love you so much, too, Liam.
I love you in whatever world we are in.
I love you so much.
I miss our kid.
I'm sure he's happy now.
[Via dela Peña rocking at the Fashion Week
in the city of love!]
Via's here?
Liam, do you want to go?
I promise, I won't let go of your hand.
Luckily, Mrs. Malvarosa knows
the organizer of this event.
She got us on the guest list.
Let's go?
Yes.
- You enjoyed it?
- Yes, we did.
Thank you so much for coming.
I appreciate you, guys.
Sorry, bro.
Wait.
I'm Attorney Hans Arevalo.
I'm from Taguig. Here's my card.
Liam Herrera.
Liam, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Joyce.
Joycelyn Trinidad.
Do you know my girlfriend?
Girlfriend?
- There she is.
- Hi, love!
Hello, love.
Wait, who are they?
Sorry, I thought you knew each other.
But they're also Filipinos.
Sorry, have we met?
No, actually,
we're just here to watch the fashion show.
We're proud to see a fellow Filipino
in the Paris Fashion Week.
Thank you.
Via.
Joyce.
Liam.
It's nice to meet you both, Joyce and Liam.
I hope we can go out together
when we return to the Philippines.
That's so nice of you.
Yes, sure.
We should take a photo.
Yes? Shall we?
Okay.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Merci.
So, let's see each other in Manila?
Of course.
Nice to meet you, guys.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations again, Miss Via.
Merci beaucoup.
I really appreciate you guys coming here.
So, we'll just go around.
Au revoir.
Be safe.
What just happened here?
I don't know, either.
So?
- Let's go?
[Fashion Week plus running around with Hans:
The Paris Adventure!]
I didn't look for them in this life.
I thought...
it would be unfair to you
if I focused on them.
You didn't even meet them.
You know what?
I'm happy.
I'm glad everything went well
because I didn't use the typewriter.
It's time for us to be happy.
I told you.
Our time will come.
I'm happy that
after everything that happened,
you're still the right one for me.
Let's go?
What's the meaning of "the right one"?
I love you so much, Tess.
[Teresita N. Buenaventura]
I hope you can forgive me...
for not being brave.
I hope my love for you can reach the heavens.
Is the right one the person who owns up
to his mistake and shortcomings?
Love, do I now look pretty on camera?
Wait.
It should be like that.
Come on, love!
You're perfect.
You're always perfect, especially for me.
- You're flattering me.
- Is it the person who's willing to forgive?
It makes me giddy. It's effective!
Okay. Let's start.
Hello, mommies!
Happy mommies and happy wives like me!
How are you guys?
Is it the one who makes amends
[Santo Cristo Park project is a gift]
when given a second chance?
[from our beloved mayor, Ramon dela Peña]
Don't put my face and name on it.
Sorry, Mayor. Don't worry.
We will strictly implement your instructions
on your next projects, sir.
I will have it removed.
That's enough.
Hello, Borj.
[My Hoodlum Lover]
Why did you use that font for the poster?
Isn't that what we agreed on?
- You said...
- Okay, okay.
I will look at it again when I get there.
- Okay. Make it faster.
- I'm on my way there.
See you.
Okay, bye.
Come on. Stop arguing.
We can talk about it and revise it.
That's right. Chill.
Okay.
- Hey!
- Guys.
I brought palabok.
Wow!
But is it really for us, boss dude, or...
for Miss Megan?
- Actually...
- You're really hot!
This is what I brought for Megan.
- That's big.
- Oh, only for her.
You can bring it home to your kid.
Special palabok for the...
Special someone!
You got it right, Deedee!
The two of you are really something else!
Stop it. Come on.
But thank you, Vergil,
for approving my suggestion
to make the movie's lead star a female.
Is it the person who knows
to listen and understand?
Perfect! Super lovely!
Thank you, my Cupcake Loves.
Thank you for
the overflowing love and support.
Is it the person who will
accept you wholeheartedly?
Whether you believe in fate or not...
in whatever mystery or magic...
the right one is the person you always choose
to be the right one for you.
The one you choose to be with you forever...
and in whatever version of your life.
Mine and your mom's love story
still went through a lot.
It is as unique as the love story
written by Ricky Lee.
It wouldn't be complete
if we didn't meet you, Dex.
Though you're not with us now...
I hope you're proud of us.
In the end, we stand by the person
who's the right one for us.
I know you're one of the stars that guide us.
We love you so much.
[The Write One: A Novel,
by William "Liam" Herrera]
Junk!
I buy and sell old stuff!